(Sheldon:)I don't see why not.
(Bernadette:)He's eating.
That's a good sign.
(Howard:)You're gonna have
to wait one hour
(Howard:)until you can go swimming again.
(laughs)
(Bernadette:)He's pretty cute.
He is.
(Howard:)Should we... name him?
(Bernadette:)It is Valentine's Day.
(Bernadette:)How about Valentino?
(Howard:)Nice. A classic rabbit name.
(both laugh)
(Howard:)Peter Rabbit, Roger Rabbit.
Valentino Wolowitz Rabbit.
(Howard:)Oh, look at all that
chest hair and overbite.
(Howard:)Of course you're a Wolowitz.
(both laugh)
Son of a bitch! He bit me!
(Bernadette:)Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay!
(Howard:)Wild rabbits
can have rabies!
(Bernadette:)Oh. Well, why did you put
your finger near its mouth?
Poor judgment, obviously.